Where are y'all getting this information?
Where are you getting the information that the Hamas Charter clearly states
that they would like to exterminate to kill all of the Jews?
Have you actually read the Hamas Charter from 2017?
Because I have, and I have some news for you.
Item 16 of the Hamas Charter, revised in 2017,
clearly states that Hamas affirms that its conflict is with the Zionist Project,
the Zionist Project of Israel, the creation of the State of Israel,
the Nakba, post-1947-1948,
not with the Jews.
Hamas affirms that its conflict is not with the Jews because of their religion.
This is not about religious persecution.
It's about the resistance of settler occupation and colonialism.
Charter point 16 goes on to say that Hamas does not wage a struggle against the Jews
because they are Jewish,
but wages a struggle against the Zionists because of their occupation of Palestine.
Now, to be clear, I am not excusing what happened on October 7th,
but I am saying we can't make the claim that Hamas Charter
says they want to kill all the Jews when the Hamas Charter makes it very,
very clear that their conflict is not with Jewish people as a faith,
not with Jews as a group.
This is the peddling of fear.
This is warmongering.
And I am not going to sit quietly by
and claim that what you're saying has any legitimacy
when I've actually read the Hamas Charter from 2017
and found that they directly contradict your claims.
The Charter goes on to say in point 17,
Hamas rejects persecution of any human being on religious grounds
and that the Jewish problem, that is, anti-Semitism and the persecution of Jews,
which they admit does happen, which they admit is a crisis,
is a product and a phenomena linked to European history
and not the history of the Arab and Muslim world.
And history would say that they're correct.
The persecution of Jews based on ethno-nationalism
was birthed in areas like Germany and Poland and Russia,
Eurocentric areas that wanted a pure white lineage
that didn't include, they thought, Jewish blood.
The Hamas Charter from 2017 makes it explicitly clear
that their struggle is against Zionism and the state of Israel
and the occupation of Palestine, not with diaspora Jews,
not with Jews as a people, not with Jews as a faith.
Claiming that Hamas is demanding the eradication of Jewish life is a lie.
It's a lie.
It's not even predicated on their literature.
Their literature directly contravenes this point.
I am not saying that Hamas hasn't caused harm.
Of course it has.
I am not saying that Jewish lives have not been lost
as a result of Hamas' violence.
Of course they have.
But Hamas' conflict is with Israel,
not diaspora Jews, not with Judaism, with Israel,
Zionism, and the occupation of Palestine.
If you guys are there as a memorial refuge in Israel,
you don't be alone.
But people would be like that,
you know,
theеф-hension of 21-year-old
and people would be like there
to be the peace of God for all.
And as a result of this,
there is astorm of 18-year-old
of a man from Israel,
one hundred years-old
of a man from Israel and by the time of Israel.
You know,
the boat's the boat and the boat
is the same for the boat.
I am not saying this,
man and the boat and the boat
is the same for the boat.
But in this time,
you know,
the boat,